<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Yuh Dead</title>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/"/>
 <updated>2019-01-03T17:56:10-07:00</updated>
 <id>http://localhost:4000</id>
 <author>
   <name>Lora Volkert</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>How Others See You</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/death/scenes/2019/01/03/description/"/>
   <updated>2019-01-03T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/death/scenes/2019/01/03/description</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today’s prompt: “Describe yourself in the third person–your physical appearance and personality–as though you were a character in a book.” [Note – I feel the second-person schtick is pretty integral to my format, so I’m just going to lean heavily into the description part.]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re dead, to begin with. But that doesn’t go far in the way of describing you. Let’s try to give you a lens on yourself, let you see yourself how others really see you. Let’s see. Uh, red, for a start. Very, very red. And kind of pulpy? Yeah. Mostly kind of a red mash, around the consistency of a cranberry chutney. Oh, sure, your bones are in there too, but even they aren’t fully intact. Your mandible’s a solid five feet away from the rest of your skull, and your femurs have been wrenched completely out of the pelvic girdle – what’s that? You don’t want to see any more? I guess I can’t blame you. Although it really is kind of a pretty shade of red.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Legacy</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/death/scenes/2019/01/02/legacy/"/>
   <updated>2019-01-02T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/death/scenes/2019/01/02/legacy</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today’s prompt: “Pick a small object to be given one day to your great-grandchild. Write a letter to that child explaining why you have chosen this object.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Dear Nathan,” you write, “The talisman enclosed in this package is called the Eye of Crathaad. It is said to be the key to unlocking the door between dimensions. That door must stay closed. That door is the one thing preventing the Old Ones from devouring all of humanity. Our family has been entrusted with keeping it safe from generation to generation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“There are those who would use the Eye to unlock the door, those who serve the Old Ones and would destroy all of humanity in the process. This is a hard life on which you now embark. You will not be able to stay too long in any one place. You must never use your true name with anyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Be cautious about who you get close to. Followers of the Old Ones are everywhere – the Order of Dagon, the Black Brotherhood, the Church of Starry Wisdom – and they won’t always be so obvious as to have pentacles tattooed on their foreheads or wear black robes with scarlet linings. They will seek you out your whole life. Keep the Eye away from them at all costs. If it should ever fall into their hands –”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You hear a dog bark. The creak of the gate. Rustling sounds. You peer out the window. There – just passing out of range of the streetlight – two figures in black hoods, with a hint of red lining. Neither of them was holding a scythe, so they must be bringing up the rear. It’s too late, then. The house is surrounded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You hear breaking glass. The unlatching of a deadbolt. The opening of a door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Eye of Crathaad gleams up at you from the desk. You grab the talisman and furiously cram it into your mouth. The stone is smooth and about the size of a walnut, but it’s mounted on some jagged gold filigree. It’s not easy to choke down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A man wearing a black robe and carrying a long scythe steps into the room just in time to see you take your last swallow. You know he knows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He’ll have to cut you to ribbons to get the Eye. But you’re pretty sure he’ll enjoy it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Baby on Board</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/death/scenes/2019/01/01/baby-on-board/"/>
   <updated>2019-01-01T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/death/scenes/2019/01/01/baby-on-board</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today’s prompt: “You have just swallowed your pride and done something you didn’t want to do. Your friend wants to know why. The two of you are driving around an almost-full parking garage looking for a space for the friend’s oversize pickup. Write the scene.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I thought you really liked Katie,” Tori says. “Wait is that – no, crap, there’s a Fiat there, couldn’t see past the bumper.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I do, but it’s just – she doesn’t want kids. I kept telling myself that it didn’t matter, that – Jesus Christ, why does everybody have to park on the fucking line – that it was fine to just be with someone fun, that I’ve got plenty of time, but I don’t have forever, y’know? But I’m definitely going to miss her.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Well, I’m sorry things didn’t work out. You guys seemed like you were good together, but I totally understand on the kids issue. You’re right – you have to do what’s right for yourself. Holy fucksticks, it’s like the whole town is parked here. Yeah, though, you can’t just put off things that are important to you. Life’s too short.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re turning the corner to head up yet another ramp when a black Hummer going way too fast for a parking garage slams into your friend’s Toyota Tundra, plowing it into a row of parked cars. You have just enough time to register a few details before you black out: the broken glass and crumpled pickup cab from where you were T-boned; the blood seeping from your forehead; and, on the back of the Hummer that has forced its way past you, a “Baby on Board” sign next to vinyl decals of a bat-winged demon, a woman, and a tiny demon.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Tradition</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/death/scenes/2018/12/31/tradition/"/>
   <updated>2018-12-31T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/death/scenes/2018/12/31/tradition</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today’s prompt: “Tell a complete stranger about a beloved family tradition.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I guess it would have started back in 1997. Aunt Harriet slipped on an icy patch and cracked her head open on a wrought-iron fence. Bled out before the ambulance arrived.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh, my,” June says. June seems to be a nice lady. She was looking forward to Midnight Mass, a little eggnog, and carolers showing up on her doorstep. And then she struck up a conversation with you at the bus stop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The tradition continued next year with Grandma Emily. That was the year we had the big blizzard. It took out power to Grandma Emily’s house for hours. She must have been convinced it wasn’t coming back on. Her garage door was open, her driver’s side door was open, and her driveway was about half-shoveled. We think she started shoveling the walk and either gave up – maybe none of her neighbors had plowed the road yet by then either – or thought to try starting her car before she went any further, and the engine didn’t turn over. Whatever happened, she must have decided to start walking. It was a long way to town from her house. They found her body in a snow bank. She literally froze to death.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“That – that’s just awful,” June says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Seems like there was one a year, every year after that, right around the holidays. Except for, I think 2003? Somewhere around there. When Uncle Bill and Aunt Connie’s car skidded on their way to a holiday party and hit a tree. Bill made it, but Connie and their daughter Nicole didn’t. So there were two that year.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh no,” June says. “How’s Bill doing now?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh, he died a few years later. Fell off the roof while he was hanging Christmas lights. I don’t think anyone was surprised. We all told him he shouldn’t be getting on the ladder for that anymore, especially not while none of us were around.” You shake your head, and smile a melancholy kind of smile. “He was always a stubborn old coot.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“My God. It must be so hard around the holidays for you and your family. Everyone’s lost so many loved ones. Everyone must be miserable when your family gets together.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Well, that’s not really an issue this year.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh, no family gathering this year?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“No. Well. It’s just that I’m the last one left.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh my God I’m so sorry. Are you okay? Do you – would you like to join my family for Christmas?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“That’s nice of you to offer, June, but I already have plans,” you say. It’s cold, and you fidget with your scarf. You must have lifted your arms enough to raise your coat above the muzzle of the pistol at your hip. June notices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You don’t have to go through with it,” she says. “You’ve obviously been through so much, more than anybody should have to. But there are people who can help you. There’s the suicide hotline, there’s therapists, there’s – please don’t do this. You don’t have to do this.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“June,” you say, standing up from the bus stop bench, “I’m sure there’s tons of people out there who want to help me out, and you could all come up with reasons for me to live. But if you think I don’t have to do this,” you say, starting towards the woods, “then you don’t know shit about tradition.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[My goal with these stories is to entertain, maybe to creep out my readers a little. But depression is a real struggle for many people and I don’t want to just breeze past that. If you’re reading this and have been contemplating suicide, please call the National Suicide Prevention Lifeline at 1-800-273-8255.]&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Umm</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/death/scenes/2018/12/30/uh-huh/"/>
   <updated>2018-12-30T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/death/scenes/2018/12/30/uh-huh</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today’s prompt: “Write a scene where the only spoken dialogue is ‘Uh-huh,’ ‘Umm,’ ‘Urrrr,’ ‘Mm-mmm’”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The young woman in the black robe with the red lining picks up a small, awl-like instrument. “Umm,” she says, then glances to her mentor, a wizened old man in an identical robe. He remains silent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The young woman cautiously holds the awl level with your eyes, the point about two inches away from your left eye.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Mmm-mmmm!” you say through your gag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The young woman looks at her mentor again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Mm-mmm,” he says, shaking his head.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The young woman lowers the awl to your throat. She palms the handle, making ready to stab with it. She looks again at her mentor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Mm-mmm,” he shakes his head again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She lowers the awl again, this time to where your hand is strapped to the arm of the chair. She raises an eyebrow and looks at her mentor again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Uh-huh,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her delicate fingers take yours for a moment, then insert the point of the awl below the nail of your index finger. You breathe deeply. Her left hand holds the awl in position. She draws back her right hand, then smacks the palm against the butt of the awl’s handle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“URRRR!” you scream through the gag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The woman looks at the man again. The old man nods his head and smiles his approval. He then points his finger at the next item on the table, a cage with a rat in it. Atop the cage sits a bowl with a knife in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You look at the table. It’s covered with a wide variety of objects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a long table.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The woman places the awl gingerly back on the table, and takes the knife out of the bowl.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a long night.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Blue Period</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/death/scenes/2018/12/29/blue/"/>
   <updated>2018-12-29T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/death/scenes/2018/12/29/blue</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today’s prompt: “What a character holding a blue object is thinking right now”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The old woman with the blue orb is thinking about what you had for dinner last night. She closes her eyes as the taste floods her mouth. The texture of each bite, the smell – she’s experiencing every last bit of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The old woman with the blue orb is thinking about the last time you were in a hospital room, pacing the halls, staring out the windows, waiting anxiously for news.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few stray black hairs nestle in the woman’s white coiffure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She’s thinking about what you looked like when you danced at a friend’s wedding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She’s thinking about your first taste of coffee, hot and bitter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She’s thinking about your first date, uncomfortable clothes and nerves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The skin smooths at the corners of her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She thinks about your swimming lessons. A day at your first job, dealing with a difficult customer. Your first kiss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The woman with the blue orb is thinking about a day you stood on the side of the road with a flat tire. A day you skinned your knee on the playground. A day you knicked yourself with a razor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The young woman with the blue orb watches as you collapse in front of her on the floor of the cave. She smiles.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Long-lost</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/death/scenes/2018/12/28/roommate/"/>
   <updated>2018-12-28T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/death/scenes/2018/12/28/roommate</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today’s prompt: “The long-lost roommate”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gideon disappeared a year and four months ago, leaving you all in the lurch. His share of the rent unpaid. His room full of his belongings. You weren’t sure how long to hold on to them. Amy suggested chucking his stuff after three weeks. Brad tried to convince you all that he’d be back, even though he’d never been gone more than two days at a time. It’s not like you hadn’t been worried. Of course you were worried. You speculated where he could be. You fielded calls from his parents when he didn’t call after months, didn’t even show up at Thanksgiving or Christmas. At first you joked that he was dead, then seriously thought he’d been in an accident. You called around to the local hospitals after the third day. Nothing. Eventually, you had to get pragmatic. After two and a half months, you split his Corn Nut stash three ways and gave all his jeans, sweatshirts and Warhammer minis to the Salvation Army. Brad’s new girlfriend moved in a couple months later, and that was that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until Gideon showed up again, his hair long and matted, his eyes yellowed and sunken, tattoos you’d never seen before covering his face. He was wearing the same clothes you last saw him in, a Pantera shirt and dark, shredded jeans, all the worse for wear. Cuffs were frayed, seams were ripped, and you could smell the clothes from feet away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Gideon,” you say, holding the apartment door open. “How are you? Where were you?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Eyes have not seen,” Gideon says, “nor ears heard.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What the fuck, man?” Brad says. “We were worried about you.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Eyes have not seen,” Gideon says, “nor ears heard.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Gideon, you’re freaking us out,” Amy says. “What’s wrong? Say something else, for fuck’s sake.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gideon steps over the threshhold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Eyes have not seen.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You back up. He steps forward again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Nor ears heard.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His right hand is busy with something at his waist. You look down. It’s a Leatherman. He keeps flicking the blade open and closed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Eyes have not seen.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Nor ears heard.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Gideon,” you laugh, a forced, nervous laugh in a register so high it surprises you, “we thought maybe you’d joined a cult or something.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Eyes have not seen.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You back up a step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Gideon, stop it,” Amy says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Nor ears. Heard.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last thing you see is Gideon’s Leatherman lunging toward your left eye.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Stolen</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/death/scenes/2018/12/27/stolen/"/>
   <updated>2018-12-27T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/death/scenes/2018/12/27/stolen</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today’s prompt: “Something you had that was stolen”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your heart, literally, as the servant of Nyarlathotep carves it out of your chest.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Ransom Note</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/death/scenes,/decapitation,/sci-fi/2018/12/26/ransom-note/"/>
   <updated>2018-12-26T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/death/scenes,/decapitation,/sci-fi/2018/12/26/ransom-note</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today’s prompt: “Tell a story that begins with a ransom note.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We have the bag of meat-flesh you have emotions for. If you want it back, put 500,000 quatloos in the Dark Matter Vortex behind the Blubby’s Burgers in Quadrant 47,” the alien that looks like a bipedal four-armed sentient burlap sack filled with cockroaches reads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Excellent, Vix-trom,” says the fat purple gelatinous alien through its fat purple gelatinous lips. “And I see you made the note from letters cut out of a publication, as is customary among the Earthen meat-sacks.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s important to get the details right,” Vix-trom says. “Speaking of which, I believe it is also tradition to cut off a part of the body and mail it with the note.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We could cut off one of the weird bony tentacles on the ends of its arms,” says the fat purple alien, entwining the fat purple jellylike tentacles at the ends of its arms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“How would the meat-flesh’s family know it came from their meat-flesh?” says Vix-trom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Ugh, all the meat-bags look the same to me,” says the fat purple alien.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I think you tell them apart by their patches of fur,” Vix-trom says, grabbing your hair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Mmmmph,” you attempt to say through your gag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We should cut off its head and send it to the meat-bag’s family,” says the fat purple alien, removing its own head with its tentacle arms. “That way, they know we have their meat-bag, and they can just reattach the head when we give them the body back,” it says, demonstrating with its own head.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Mmmm mmmm!” you say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Good idea,” says Vix-trom. Its lower right arm produces a thin, gleaming blade and slashes all the way through your neck. Your head hits the floor with a thud and your body slumps in its chains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Is it dead?” says the fat purple alien. “Stupid meat-sacks.”&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Rocket Man</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/death/scenes,/best/day,/sci-fi/2018/12/25/astronaut/"/>
   <updated>2018-12-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/death/scenes,/best/day,/sci-fi/2018/12/25/astronaut</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today’s prompt: “You are an astronaut. Describe your perfect day.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The day couldn’t have started better. Somehow, hidden in all the packages of freeze-dried creamed spinach and chicken teriyaki, there was a packet of beef enchiladas and, wonder of wonders, some shrimp cocktail. You could have sworn you were out of the good stuff. Maybe the beef enchilada fairy visited overnight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conditions were perfect for the descent to Mars. You and Maria take the lander down to the surface. It touches down as smoothly as a fat snowflake nestling in the branch of a fir tree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Let’s draw straws for who gets to go first,” Maria says. She produces two foil strips she’s saved from the tops of food packets, one trimmed shorter than the other. She turns her back to you, fiddling with the strips, then turns back around, the two ends poking out of her fist at an equal height. You suck in your breath and pick the one on the left. She opens her hand and holds up her strip, showing you she has the short one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Lucky bastard,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You step out of the lander. The surface is curiously springy, the powdery dust giving way below your footsteps. Despite the bulk of your space suit, you feel exhilarated. Maria follows, and then Paul, Aubrey and Colin from the other lander. You all set to work connecting pieces of the base.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You look up, shading your eyes against the sun’s glare. Deimos and Phobos are both out in the orange-y sky. It’s breathtaking. Your heart swells. You’re the first ones. The first humans on this planet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You and Maria hop back aboard your lander to head back to the orbiter for more equipment. As you lift off, you hear a clank. You radio to Aubrey, who’s pulling the last of the gear out of the second lander, “I think I heard something as we took off. Can you see anything out of order on the outside of our lander?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I can’t see anything from here. Have Scott check you out as you get closer,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You relay the same message to Scott up in the orbiter, and he agrees to keep an eye out as you ascend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re almost to the orbiter when Scott radios down, “I can see it now. The docking mechanism came loose. It’s still partly attached, but you’ll need to rebolt the one side. Easy fix.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You want to handle it?” Maria says. “I know you love your space walks.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You do love your space walks. When you rode roller coasters as a kid, at the moment before the big drop, you always wondered if walking out in space alongside your ship would feel like that. But fixing a broken part on the outside of a spacecraft is like free climbing in Zero G. It’s intense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ve just reattached the docking mechanism when Maria calls out, “There’s something wrong with the controls. The fuel – I can’t–”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any further explanation is immediately cut off. The lander burns through a sudden burst of rocket fuel and jolts toward the orbiter. Your torque wrench is long gone. You’re lucky to hold on to the railing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The lander hits the side of the orbiter with a crumpling sound, then pulls away. “Maria?” you call out on your radio. “Maria!” No one answers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You work your way to the lander’s door and pound on it. “Maria!” No response. Frantically, you pound with both fists. You’re not even trying not to cry, even though you know your tears have nowhere to go. You beat both fists against the door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which is when you notice the frayed end of your broken tether float past your face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You reach for the railing, but it’s already too far away.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Facebook Statuses from the Far Year 2023</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/death/scenes,/lovecraft/2018/12/24/facebook/"/>
   <updated>2018-12-24T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/death/scenes,/lovecraft/2018/12/24/facebook</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today’s prompt: “Write Facebook status updates from the year 2017.” (The book was published in 2012.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“TFW you didn’t get any sleep last night because your neighbors were up all night chanting ‘Cthulhu R’lyeh wgah’nagl fhtagn.’”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The liberal media doesn’t want you to know that Hillary’s email server was hiding direct communications with Cthulhu himself. WAKE UP SHEEPLE!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buzzfeed article: “20 Reasons Why the Ascendancy of Our Dread Lord Cthulhu Might Not Be as Bad as You Think.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Facebook posts cease as, much like all its users, the site dies on Aug. 17, 2023.]&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Buck Up, Houseplant</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/death/scenes,/bleeding/out/2018/12/23/houseplant/"/>
   <updated>2018-12-23T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/death/scenes,/bleeding/out/2018/12/23/houseplant</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today’s prompt: “A houseplant is dying. Tell it why it needs to live.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You’ve got to be strong. You’ve got to carry on.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The philodrendon’s yellowed leaves and wilting stem are unaffected by your pleas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Come on, plant, you have to live! After all,” you sputter, the blood from your throat pooling around the philodrendon’s pot, “one of us has to.”&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Worst Thanksgiving</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/death/scenes,/poison/2018/12/22/worst-thanksgiving/"/>
   <updated>2018-12-22T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/death/scenes,/poison/2018/12/22/worst-thanksgiving</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today’s prompt: “The worst Thanksgiving dish you ever had”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The green bean casserole, heavy on the strychnine.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>What Can Happen in a Second</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/death/scenes/2018/12/21/what-can-happen-in-a-second/"/>
   <updated>2018-12-21T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/death/scenes/2018/12/21/what-can-happen-in-a-second</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today’s prompt: “What can happen in a second”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The slash of a knife. A blow to the head. Your last gasp. The plunge into midair as the gallows trapdoor opens beneath you. A bullet ripping through your torso. A final shiver down your spine. A snap of monstrous jaws.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Death comes for us all, relentlessly, tick by tick by tick of the clock. I don’t know how you’ll die, whether your whole death encompasses a single second, or your last moment comes after long months of building agony. But I have a feeling, based on the cabal of people after your hide, that your last second will be memorable.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
